let's look at the answer to our quiz
what kind of application gets no benefit
from miss under miss support
one that always hits in the cache gets
no benefit it never has misses so it
cannot benefit from misunder miss
support
an application that misses every 1000
instructions will have a miss and the
processor will run out of rob entries
because it has fewer than 1000
until it finds the next miss so that
application will suffer the first miss
and only then the processor can continue
and find the next miss so we never
actually need to do miss under miss so
this application will not benefit
an application that has a miss every 10
instructions will have a miss and we'll
find the next miss so it can benefit
from miss under miss support so this
should not be checked and then an
application that has a miss every two
instructions of course will also benefit
from miss undermiss so we don't check
this either